<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 04:13:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 05:33:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/overview/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Docs is currently in the pre-release stage of development and, therefore, is not recommended for use in production. You&amp;rsquo;re welcome to try out the theme yourself, and contributions to the project a very welcome.
Welcome to the Lotus Docs user guide. This guide shows you how to start creating technical documentation sites using Lotus Docs, including site customisation and using Lotus Docs&amp;rsquo; features and templates.
What is Lotus Docs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickstart</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 19:25:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>Requirements link git Go ≥ v1.19 Hugo ≥ v0.100.0 (Extended Version) Install Hugo linkInstall the Hugo CLI, using the specific instructions for your operating system below:
Linux Homebrew (macOS) Windows (Chocolatey) Windows (Scoop) Your Linux distro’s package manager may include Hugo. If this is the case, install it directly using your distro’s package manager – for instance, in Ubuntu, run the following command. This will install the extended edition of Hugo:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      <description>Code Highlighters linkLotus Docs supports syntax highlighting by Prism (enabled by default via param.docs.prism in hugo.toml) or Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in code highlighter Chroma.
Fenced code blocks (code enclosed by triple backticks above and below) that specify a code language (declared right of the opening fence), will automatically highlight the code content as HTML e.g. ```html:
```html &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Buy cool new product&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Use action=&amp;#34;/create-checkout-session.php&amp;#34; if your server is PHP based.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plausible Analytics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/plausible-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/plausible-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Plausible Analytics is a simple, open source, lightweight (&amp;lt; 1 KB), privacy-focused alternative to Google Analytics. Plausible is completely independent, self-funded and bootstrapped. Read more about Plausible Analytics.
Why use Plausible Analytics? linkAs previously mentioned, Plausible is an open source, privacy-focused Google Analytics alternative. So what are the benefits of this?
Privacy by design - Plausible, by design complies with strict privacy policies. Including: GDPR, CCPA, and PECR. You own your data - Plausible does not sell or share your data, or abuse your visitor&amp;rsquo;s privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics v4</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 23:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Docs utilises Hugo&amp;rsquo;s internal Google Analytics v4 template1.
Enabling Google Analytics linkTo enable Google Analytics v4, simply provide your tracking ID in your configuration file:
hugo.toml hugo.yaml hugo.json googleAnalytics = &amp;#39;G-MEASUREMENT_ID&amp;#39; googleAnalytics: G-MEASUREMENT_ID { &amp;#34;googleAnalytics&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;G-MEASUREMENT_ID&amp;#34; } Hugo Google Analytics v4 Internal Template - gohugo.io&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback Widget</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/feedback-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/feedback-widget/</guid>
      <description>The Lotus Docs feedback plugin integrates with Google or Plausible Analytics to allow you to collect visitor feedback on your sites&amp;rsquo; content.
Why use web analytics to collect feedback? linkShort answer? Because it&amp;rsquo;s FREE! Other benefits include:
No need to sign up to yet another service just to collect basic visitor feedback. Easy to configure. Once Google or Plausible Analytics (or both) are configured in hugo.toml, the Feedback Widget it ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FlexSearch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/flexsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/flexsearch/</guid>
      <description>What is FlexSearch? linkFlexSearch is a Static Search plugin that provides a fast and simple search experience for your Lotus Docs site. Static Search provides instant, dynamic results for any search terms, and includes a wealth of options and settings to fine-tune the functionality to best suit the needs of your site visitors.
How does FlexSearch work? linkFlexSearch works via a mechanism known as Contextual Search (invented by Thomas Wilkerling).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DocSearch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/docsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 14:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/docsearch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;UTF-8&#34;?&gt; What is DocSearch? linkDocSearch is a unique, free search plugin, specifically designed for technical documentation for open-source projects or technical blogs. Providing fast, accurate search options, DocSearch empowers visitors to find the information they need as quickly as possible. With the DocSearch plugin enabled, integrating search into your Lotus Docs site takes just a few moments.
How does DocSearch work? linkMuch like other search engines, DocSearch uses a scraper to index your site content; in simple terms, the scraper scans your website and stores the data, which it can then collate to make a custom search that is effective for your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KaTex</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/katex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 20:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/features/katex/</guid>
      <description>$$ f\relax{x} = \int_{-\infty}^\infty \hat f(\xi)\ e^{2 \pi i \xi x} \ d\xi $$
How to use KaTex with Lotus Docs linkKaTex support is controlled by the katex parameter in your front matter (line 10 below). Add and set it to true in your front matter to enable KaTex support for that page. This means KaTex support and resources are active only for pages that require it.
--- weight: 530 title: &amp;#34;KaTex&amp;#34; description: &amp;#34;Fast Tex math rendering for your Lotus Docs site&amp;#34; icon: &amp;#34;function&amp;#34; date: &amp;#34;2023-08-26T20:43:23&amp;#43;01:00&amp;#34; lastmod: &amp;#34;2023-08-26T20:43:23&amp;#43;01:00&amp;#34; draft: true toc: true katex: true --- Writing LaTex in Markdown linkEquations can be displayed either in block level or inline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breadcrumb Navigation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/theme-options/breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 07:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/theme-options/breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;UTF-8&#34;?&gt;/ Guides / Theme Options / Breadcrumbs Enable Breadcrumbs linkBreadcrumb navigation is enabled by default1 and appears in the top right-hand corner of content pages above the page title. The Lotus Docs breadcrumb implementation functions with both multilingual and single-language sites.
Structured Data linkThe breadcrumb navigation also auto-generates structured data for rich results to help enable search results that are more engaging to users. Here are the Breadcrumb Rich Results test results for this very page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alerts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/alerts/</guid>
      <description>Adding a Page Alert linkPage alerts can be added to your markdown using the following shortcode:
{{&amp;lt; alert text=&amp;#34;This is the default alert. It consists of a default theme colour and icon.&amp;#34; /&amp;gt;}} The above code results in the following alert:
notifications This is the default alert. It consists of a default theme colour and icon. Alert with Context linkAdd context to an alert via the context parameter:
{{&amp;lt; alert context=&amp;#34;info&amp;#34; text=&amp;#34;This is an alert with an &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;info&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tables</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 04:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/tables/</guid>
      <description>The table shortcode enables Lotus Docs to take advantage of Bootstrap&amp;rsquo;s opt-in table styling.
Regular Tables linkBy default Lotus Docs renders regular Markdown tables with some very basic styling:
| Tables | Are | Cool | |----------|:-------------:|------:| | col 1 is | left-aligned | $1600 | | col 2 is | centered | $12 | | col 3 is | right-aligned | $1 | Result:
Tables Are Cool col 1 is left-aligned $1600 col 2 is centered $12 col 3 is right-aligned $1 Shortcode Tables linkThe the table shortcode allows you to implement a number of Bootstrap&amp;rsquo;s table styling classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tabs</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/tabs/</guid>
      <description>The tabs shortcode leverages Bootstrap&amp;rsquo;s Tabs styling to easily add Tabs to your markdown content. The shortcode is actually a combination of two separate shortcodes (tab and tabs) working together.
You need a minimum of one tab shortcode nested inside a tabs shortcode for the component to function:
{{&amp;lt; tabs tabTotal=&amp;#34;1&amp;#34;&amp;gt;}} {{% tab tabName=&amp;#34;Tab 1&amp;#34; %}} **Tab 1 Content** {{% /tab %}} {{&amp;lt; /tabs &amp;gt;}} Basic Tabs linkThe following example demonstrates how to create a basic multi tab navigation component using the tabs and tab shortcodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prism</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/prism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 04:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/prism/</guid>
      <description>Prism Shortcode linkWhen Prism is enabled in hugo.toml syntax highlighting can also be achieved using a paired Prism shortcode. The code language is declared using the lang parameter:
{{&amp;lt; prism lang=&amp;#34;html&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Buy cool new product&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Use action=&amp;#34;/create-checkout-session.php&amp;#34; if your server is PHP based. --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;form action=&amp;#34;/create-checkout-session&amp;#34; method=&amp;#34;POST&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;button type=&amp;#34;submit&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Checkout&amp;lt;/button&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/form&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/html&amp;gt; {{&amp;lt; /prism &amp;gt;}} All code blocks highlighted by Prism feature the Copy to Clipboard Button plugin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdownify</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/markdownify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/markdownify/</guid>
      <description>This shortcode parses its content as markdown.
Usage linkThe following:
{{&amp;lt; markdownify &amp;gt;}} **Bold Text**: Above a code block. ```html &amp;lt;!-- An example HTML code block --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Hello World&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt; {{&amp;lt; /markdownify &amp;gt;}} Renders:
Bold Text: Above a code block.
&amp;lt;!-- An example HTML code block --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Hello World&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt; Nested Shortcodes linkThe markdownify shortcode is especially useful in cases where you require portions of content nested inside another shortcode be parsed as Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KaTex</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/katex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 04:13:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/guides/shortcodes/katex/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Docs has built-in support for KaTex. However, there are certain equation syntaxes which do not render well if at all without a lot of character escaping1 or alterations. The KaTex shortcode is suited to handle such cases.
For example:
{{&amp;lt; katex &amp;gt;}} $$ \begin{array} {lcl} L(p,w_i) &amp;amp;=&amp;amp; \dfrac{1}{N}\Sigma_{i=1}^N(\underbrace{f_r(x_2 \rightarrow x_1 \rightarrow x_0)G(x_1 \longleftrightarrow x_2)f_r(x_3 \rightarrow x_2 \rightarrow x_1)}_{sample\, radiance\, evaluation\, in\, stage2} \\\\\\ &amp;amp;=&amp;amp; \prod_{i=3}^{k-1}(\underbrace{\dfrac{f_r(x_{i+1} \rightarrow x_i \rightarrow x_{i-1})G(x_i \longleftrightarrow x_{i-1})}{p_a(x_{i-1})}}_{stored\,in\,vertex\, during\,light\, path\, tracing\, in\, stage1})\dfrac{G(x_k \longleftrightarrow x_{k-1})L_e(x_k \rightarrow x_{k-1})}{p_a(x_{k-1})p_a(x_k)}) \end{array} $$ {{&amp;lt; /katex &amp;gt;}} renders as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/reference/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 16:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/reference/configuration/</guid>
      <description>A list of available configuration settings in the site configuration file, hugo.toml, hugo.yaml, or hugo.json:
[params] linkGoogle Fonts link Parameter Type Default Value Description google_fonts array N/A An array of Google fonts and sizes to load. e.g.google_fonts = [[&amp;quot;Inter&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;300, 400, 600, 700&amp;quot;],[&amp;quot;Fira Code&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;500, 700&amp;quot;]] This will load the Google Inter and Fira Code fonts in the specified sizes. sans_serif_font string System Font Set the Sans Serif font. e.g. &amp;quot;Inter&amp;quot; secondary_font string System Font Set the Secondary font.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Contribute</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 21:49:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to code linkCreate a Pull Request link Follow the GitHub flow. Follow the Conventional Commits Specification Improve documentation link Follow the GitHub flow. Follow the Conventional Commits Specification Create an issue link Bug report Feature request Help others linkLotus Docs Discussions is the place to get help and help others with Lotus Docs.
Submit to showcase linkShare what you’ve built with us.
Contribute financially linkHelp support the team developing Lotus Docs by becoming a financial contributor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Contributions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</guid>
      <description>We use Open Collective to receive contributions, share our budget, and manage expenses. Visit the Lotus Labs Open Collective page.
Become a Sponsor linkBecome a sponsor starting at $50.00 per month. Your logo — with a link to your website — will show up on the Lotus Docs website, the Lotus Docs repository, and the Lotus Labs Open Collective page.
Become a Backer linkBecome a backer starting at $5.00 per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Our Pledge linkWe as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/help/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/help/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/help/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/help/faqs/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
