<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 01:04:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      <description>Code Highlighters linkLotus Docs supports syntax highlighting by Prism (enabled by default via param.docs.prism in hugo.toml) or Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in code highlighter Chroma.
Fenced code blocks (code enclosed by triple backticks above and below) that specify a code language (declared right of the opening fence), will automatically highlight the code content as HTML e.g. ```html:
```html &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Buy cool new product&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Use action=&amp;#34;/create-checkout-session.php&amp;#34; if your server is PHP based.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plausible Analytics</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/plausible-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/plausible-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Plausible Analytics is a simple, open source, lightweight (&amp;lt; 1 KB), privacy-focused alternative to Google Analytics. Plausible is completely independent, self-funded and bootstrapped. Read more about Plausible Analytics.
Why use Plausible Analytics? linkAs previously mentioned, Plausible is an open source, privacy-focused Google Analytics alternative. So what are the benefits of this?
Privacy by design - Plausible, by design complies with strict privacy policies. Including: GDPR, CCPA, and PECR. You own your data - Plausible does not sell or share your data, or abuse your visitor&amp;rsquo;s privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics v4</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 23:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Lotus Docs utilises Hugo&amp;rsquo;s internal Google Analytics v4 template1.
Enabling Google Analytics linkTo enable Google Analytics v4, simply provide your tracking ID in your configuration file:
hugo.toml hugo.yaml hugo.json googleAnalytics = &amp;#39;G-MEASUREMENT_ID&amp;#39; googleAnalytics: G-MEASUREMENT_ID { &amp;#34;googleAnalytics&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;G-MEASUREMENT_ID&amp;#34; } Hugo Google Analytics v4 Internal Template - gohugo.io&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback Widget</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/feedback-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/feedback-widget/</guid>
      <description>The Lotus Docs feedback plugin integrates with Google or Plausible Analytics to allow you to collect visitor feedback on your sites&amp;rsquo; content.
Why use web analytics to collect feedback? linkShort answer? Because it&amp;rsquo;s FREE! Other benefits include:
No need to sign up to yet another service just to collect basic visitor feedback. Easy to configure. Once Google or Plausible Analytics (or both) are configured in hugo.toml, the Feedback Widget it ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FlexSearch</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/flexsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/flexsearch/</guid>
      <description>What is FlexSearch? linkFlexSearch is a Static Search plugin that provides a fast and simple search experience for your Lotus Docs site. Static Search provides instant, dynamic results for any search terms, and includes a wealth of options and settings to fine-tune the functionality to best suit the needs of your site visitors.
How does FlexSearch work? linkFlexSearch works via a mechanism known as Contextual Search (invented by Thomas Wilkerling).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DocSearch</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/docsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 14:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/docsearch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;UTF-8&#34;?&gt; What is DocSearch? linkDocSearch is a unique, free search plugin, specifically designed for technical documentation for open-source projects or technical blogs. Providing fast, accurate search options, DocSearch empowers visitors to find the information they need as quickly as possible. With the DocSearch plugin enabled, integrating search into your Lotus Docs site takes just a few moments.
How does DocSearch work? linkMuch like other search engines, DocSearch uses a scraper to index your site content; in simple terms, the scraper scans your website and stores the data, which it can then collate to make a custom search that is effective for your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KaTex</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/katex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 20:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/guides/features/katex/</guid>
      <description>$$ f\relax{x} = \int_{-\infty}^\infty \hat f(\xi)\ e^{2 \pi i \xi x} \ d\xi $$
How to use KaTex with Lotus Docs linkKaTex support is controlled by the katex parameter in your front matter (line 10 below). Add and set it to true in your front matter to enable KaTex support for that page. This means KaTex support and resources are active only for pages that require it.
--- weight: 530 title: &amp;#34;KaTex&amp;#34; description: &amp;#34;Fast Tex math rendering for your Lotus Docs site&amp;#34; icon: &amp;#34;function&amp;#34; date: &amp;#34;2023-08-26T20:43:23&amp;#43;01:00&amp;#34; lastmod: &amp;#34;2023-08-26T20:43:23&amp;#43;01:00&amp;#34; draft: true toc: true katex: true --- Writing LaTex in Markdown linkEquations can be displayed either in block level or inline.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
