<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributing on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributing on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 02:21:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Contribute</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 21:49:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</guid>
      <description>Contribute to code linkCreate a Pull Request link Follow the GitHub flow. Follow the Conventional Commits Specification Improve documentation link Follow the GitHub flow. Follow the Conventional Commits Specification Create an issue link Bug report Feature request Help others linkLotus Docs Discussions is the place to get help and help others with Lotus Docs.
Submit to showcase linkShare what you’ve built with us.
Contribute financially linkHelp support the team developing Lotus Docs by becoming a financial contributor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Contributions</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/financial-contributions/</guid>
      <description>We use Open Collective to receive contributions, share our budget, and manage expenses. Visit the Lotus Labs Open Collective page.
Become a Sponsor linkBecome a sponsor starting at $50.00 per month. Your logo — with a link to your website — will show up on the Lotus Docs website, the Lotus Docs repository, and the Lotus Labs Open Collective page.
Become a Backer linkBecome a backer starting at $5.00 per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rapidai.github.io/LabelConvert/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Our Pledge linkWe as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
